#### Md. Milon Hossain

Software Developer at Tech Village

milon.cse.bubt@gmail.com

### Summary

Experienced Web Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in Object-Oriented Programming (OOP), Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), PHP, JavaScript, and jQuery. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.) in focused in Computer Science and Engineering(CSE) from Bangladesh University of Business and Technology(BUBT).

## Experience

Software Developer at Tech Village January 2018 - Present

Freelancer Web Developer January 2017 - Present

#### Education

Bangladesh University of Business and Technology(BUBT)
Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.) in, Computer Science and Engineering(CSE), 2012 - 2017
Jahangirpur Govt. College
H.S.C, Science, 2011 - 2012
Aihai High School
S.S.C, Science, 2009 - 2010

# Md. Milon Hossain

Software Developer at Tech Village

milon.cse.bubt@gmail.com



Contact Md. Milon on LinkedIn